It's possible that
this is the new operational site
of La Morte Bianca in the Philippines.
The Concordat.
Their goal is to establish
an administration here in the Philippines,
and spread their terror from here.
They immediately found the site
that Isabella
purchased as their stronghold.
It's like… it's raining a bit.
-Mikoy, what…
-It's drizzling?
-So annoying.
-Is this it?
It's raining!
Hey, what is it?
We already had a census last year.
Let's go, let's go.
You're new here.
We need to talk to one of their people.
You've got some nerve,
stealing inside a mafia house.
And you're even copying me.
Bok.
What's that? Do you have a problem?
I'm just worried.
What if,
Chiara doesn't just want
to reconnect for information.
And what if she gets to
talk to her father again,
and she'll be convinced to come back.
Bok, is what you're feeling,
a gut feeling?
Is it coming from your heart?
Do you think she could betray us?
Like that?
I don't know, I'm not sure, but
this isn't about my gut anymore.
I'm just basing it on facts.
She's a mob boss, and she grew up
in a crime syndicate.
So she's used to betrayal.
Okay, so you think
Chiara could betray Mikoy?
She wouldn't do that.
I get why you're worried.
I get why it's hard to trust.
But she wouldn't do that.
Chiara isn't perfect.
And she isn't kind all the time either.
But her heart isn't bad.
You know, deep inside,
all Chiara really wants
is a quiet and simple life.
She never dreamed of becoming a criminal.
Her dream is to be free.
Agent Alex, you witnessed it yourself.
You saw how she left everything behind.
Family, name, protection,
status… what for?
What I hold on to is,
she loves me.
And that's what she chose.
You could've just said you were hungry.
Chiara.
By how she was raised. Does it matter?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard when,
you love someone
who doesn't love you back.
Because it hurts.
You know you're drunk.
I'm not drunk, Bok, okay?
I still know what I'm saying.
I'm just a little confused.
There are so many people in the world.
But why do you end up liking someone
who could never like you back?
Good thing I don't have time for that.
Because that kind of stupidity
can make you do crazy things.
-Agent Sianong.
-Hey!
And your designated driver
still has work tomorrow.
Let's go!
Okay, fine.
But first, I have a speech.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Go.
Hurry up.
In a guy? What do you like?
I like someone who's, a bit tall.
How about personality?
What's my favorite song?
The one you always sing.
What?
"We Are in Love" by Taylor Swift.
See? Why is he invested?
Why does he have so many questions?
Why does he know your favorite song?
Why not?
As you said, he's observant.
Use your brain.
Be a good judge of character that you are.
What if it's nothing.
What if he's just a kind person.
What if you're the only one
who's putting a meaning on it?
So what if I am?
I'm in love.
And people in love can be foolish.
And that's okay.
Besides,
if he wants to get to know me better,
why would I stop him?
Can we talk?
Well, that's early.
Sorry, I know it's early, but,
about last night.
Mikoy.
I'm not saying
you should trust her right away.
I'm not saying everything
Chiara does is right either.
Alex, I know it's hard.
If I were in your position,
I'd probably feel the same way.
Alex, I hope you'll also consider
the choices she's made here.
Because she's given up so much.
And that wasn't easy.
Mikoy, in our line of work,
trust doesn't come easy.
Because when we're wrong,
people get hurt and put in danger.
I can't promise that I'll trust her.
But I'll try.
Thank you.
PINAGPALA
SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Luisa Mae.
Sorry about yesterday.
I was just helping Laurence.
Research.
But don't think that,
I like Sofie.
That was just wingman duties.
What?
Why didn't you just say so right away?
You know, that is so, so cute.
Here, look at this.
There!
You know, I've really wanted to go there.
I've been looking at it for days.
And now,
it's perfect!
Perfect for what?
There's a beach,
an island,
and camping.
Right? And they say
the signal is weak there.
Which means people
won't be on their phones much.
Plus, we get the chance
to clean the shore too.
Right?
Imagine the sunset there.
I mean, if it works out.
We'll help the environment,
and help their love life too.
It's a win-win for us, right?
Wingman! Nice!
That could work.
There.
Look.
Maybe this place could work too.
Quiet, fresh air. Beautiful.
And most importantly, hours away
from that crazy woman.
Only Chiara's missing.
I wish she were here.
At least there won't be any more
random midnight meetings.
No more obsession with A5 steak.
No more world domination plans
in the middle of the night.
Listen. Let's just smile.
Help out when needed.
Sightseeing.
Then after we're back on shore,
-after we settled,
-Donabel…
Donabel!
Good, you're here.
Follow me.
Let's go.
If we're wrong,
we create chaos.
If we're right,
they create even bigger chaos.
Huh? I have my own room?
People will move them.
Sir, we have a proposal.
Chiara wants to reconnect
with Viktor Valtrovi.
-To get the information …
-No!
Sir, please hear us out first.
It's possible Viktor knows the locations
of La Morte Bianca's operations.
And if we need to obtain information,
then we have to consider it.
What you're asking me is,
to allow Chiara,
to reconnect with the same
criminal organization that raised her,
trained her, protected her,
manipulated her.
The very people who spent her entire life
telling her what's right and wrong.
And you want me to believe
they can't do that to her again?
Just one conversation.
Just a clarification, just a talk.
No feelings involved.
It's like a toxic ex.
Just a clarification, no feelings at all.
But next thing you know,
they're back together.
Not because they're bad,
but because they think they're in control.
What if Chiara is right?
And even Viktor still cares?
I notice that there are
cars roaming around here.
Even motorcycles riding in tandem.
Actually even people are wandering here.
I don't feel good about it.
I want to talk to Papa.
Of course I also want to give something.
-What happened?
-I slept so well.
Hold on, where are Mikoy and Chiara?